{
    "subject": "resource/Ringwood_Secondary_College",
    "predicate": "ontology/officialSchoolColour",
    "object": "Maroon & Green",
    "human_readable": "The official school colours of Ringwood Secondary College are Maroon and Green.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9856308102607727,
            "question": "Is Maroon one of the official school colours of Ringwood Secondary College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.968845009803772,
            "question": "What are the official school colors of Ringwood Secondary College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.939475417137146,
            "question": "Do Green and Maroon represent Ringwood Secondary College's identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8908888697624207,
            "question": "If someone were to wear the official school colors of Ringwood Secondary College, what colors would they be wearing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8897303342819214,
            "question": "Are Red and Blue the official school colours of Ringwood Secondary College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8862106800079346,
            "question": "Besides Green, what other color represents Ringwood Secondary College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8637393712997437,
            "question": "Can you name the two school colours for Ringwood Secondary College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8374200463294983,
            "question": "What color combination is associated with Ringwood Secondary College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8362306952476501,
            "question": "Which two colors represent Ringwood Secondary College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6866104006767273,
            "question": "What colors are used in the logo or uniform of Ringwood Secondary College?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The official school colours of Ringwood Secondary College are Maroon and Green.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2402_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which two colors represent Ringwood Secondary College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2402_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What color combination is associated with Ringwood Secondary College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2402_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name the two school colours for Ringwood Secondary College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2402_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2402_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2402_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2402_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2402_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2402_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2402_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2402_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2402_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2402_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2402_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is explicitly stated that the school colours of Ringwood Secondary College are indeed Maroon & Green."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that the \"colours\" of Ringwood Secondary College are \"Maroon & Green,\" which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}